Welcome to MarvelousDesigner's tutorial video of home appliances.
In this tutorial, we will make a simple flat bed.
First, open the project file. The file can be downloaded from the link in the description.
After opening, select objects other than the bed, turn on the fire, and then hide them.
Then, in the front shadow of the bed sheet in the window of the second floor, create a rectangular sheet.
This sheet should be slightly larger than the front shadow, so that it is convenient to wrap the bedhead.
In the 3D window, click on the sheet, and the positioning tool will appear.
Click on the positioning tool in the upper right corner, and then click on the bedhead.
You can move the sheet quickly to the area near the bedhead.
Right-click on the single-click sheet.
Select the inner part of the bedhead layer.
There will be a connected sheet that has been sewed.
In the 3D window, arrange the sheets of the bedhead layer.
Put the bedsheet in the middle.
Use the circular line tool to drag the four corners of the sheet to create a circular line.
In the process of dragging, click on the right mouse button to enter a specific value.
Since the sheets of the bedhead layer have a link, the other sheet will also be modified at the same time.
After opening the model, the two sheets are mixed together.
And the bedhead is wrapped.
Because the particle diameter is relatively large, the sheet has a gap between the model and the model, so the particle diameter is reduced.
The particle diameter is different from the symmetrical relationship.
The particle diameter of the linked sheet is not linked.
Therefore, both sheets must be reduced to the particle diameter.
Now open the model, the sheet will no longer penetrate.
Save the project file.
The post-sewing model will be modified on this basis.
Please save and see the user manual.
If you're not using the post-sewing one, I recommend we use the post-seeing application.
If you are not using the post-sewing application, please refer to the user manual.
It's the best to use a shape calculator or a sketchbook.
From here, if you do not have a sketchbook, you can use the one I showed you here.
Think about the model of the sheet you want to use.
You can call the product by the name of the model you want to use it.
Just write the name of the product.
Then copy the model code and bring it down with your fingers.
This time, we will use the sheet with a focal length of 1 cm.